

#### **HALIDI**

Bachelor Degree in Project Management-Internship

- Dar es salaam
- **L** 0714059160
- ► halidiselemani94@gmail.com
- Tanzanian
- **Male**

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Halidi Maneno is a software engineer with experience in developing software. He is also a computer vision researcher at Africa4ai Collab who believes in new technology to change and solve community problems. His work focused on transforming the business through Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence .

# **Career Objective**

database design, database development, system development, system design, data analysis, machine learning, system test

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2023

Dar Es Salaam, Mikocheni

## exact manpower

Bachelor Degree in ProjectManagement-Internship

exact manpower 2021 - 2023

### **EDUCATION**

**Software Engineering:** 2015 - 2021

Bachelors degree, university of Dodoma (UDOM)

Software Developer: 2023 - 2023

A-Level, udom

Advanced diploma in business Administration and Marketing:

2024 - 2024

Advanced Diploma, Institute of Finance Management

**SKILLS** 

Results Organizational

**Authority Organizational** 

